

CONTACT

✓ Masaru.yamada9277@gmail.com

Shibuya City, Tokyo

EDUCATION

2011 - 2016 UNIVERSITY OF TOKYO

• Bachelor's Degree

SKILLS

- Javascript
- TypeScript
- React
- React Native
- Next.js
- GraphQL
- Express.js
- FastAPI
- Django
- Supabase
- Go
- MySQL
- PostgreSQL
- DynamoDB
- Pytorch
- Pandas
- Scikit-Learn
- LLMs

LANGUAGES

- Japanese (Fluent)
- English (Intermediate)

MASARU YAMADA

SENIOR SOFRWARE ENGINEER

PROFILE

I am a full-stack JS software engineer experienced in creating single-page web applications, mobile apps, and web services using JavaScript, React, React Native and Node.js. Proficient in developing client-side applications based on the blockchain technology. Experienced in developing web applications for the currency exchange, healthcare, ecommerce, and travelling domains.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Cosomil

September 2021 - Present

Senior Software Engineer

- · Leading prefessional growth of newcomers in Javascript department
- Performing R&D tasks on the projects to support incremental technology updates
- Deveoloping client side of web and mobile app with React, Next.js, React Native and Redux
- Implementing complex, responsive, and adaptive web interfaces

Yanekara

December 2018 - September 2021

Fullstack Engineer

- Developing client side of web and mobile apps with React, React Native and Redux
- Developing server side web and mobile apps with Django, FastAPI
- Implementing complex, responsive, and adaptive web interfaces

CodLUCK Technology JSC

May 2017 - December 2018

Javascript Software Engineer

- Implementing client-side applications with React, Next.js and Redux
- Developing responsive user inferfaces with Twitter Bootstrap and SCSS
- Developing the event-driven client-side applications using Websockets

Computools

November 2016 - May 2017

Javascript Software Engineer

- Developing the event-driven client-side applications using the WebSocket API
- Creating responsive web interfaces using Styled Components and LESS
- · Building client-side applications with React, Redux, and Saga